(Leonard:)Not really.
(Penny:)But you're curious
about aluminum cans.
(Penny:)You're a weird
little guy.
(Sheldon:)That's it. The Sheldon Cooper
Girlfriend Challenge
(Sheldon:)is officially live.
(chuckles)
(Howard:)Congratulations.
This is exciting.
(Sheldon:)Right now,
(Sheldon:)somewhere, a woman
is dividing the atomic weight
(Sheldon:)of the best noble gas
by the number of colors
(Sheldon:)in the oldest national flag still in use...
Then using
(Howard:)that number as the average speed
to calculate the travel time
(Howard:)from Mordor to the Shire.
And...
(Sheldon:)taking her first step
towards a lifetime
(Sheldon:)of laughter,
love and, best of all, rules.
I-I hope we didn't make
the puzzles too hard.
(Howard:)Well... if she can solve them,
it'll prove she's intelligent,
(Howard:)tenacious and...
so socially awkward
(Howard:)she has nothing better to do
on a Saturday night.
(Sheldon:)Golly, she sounds
too good to be true.
(Tall British Dave:)This is fun.
I haven't dated much
(Tall British Dave:)since my divorce.
(Amy:)Well, I'm having
a good time, too.